Contact

ma9da.ahmed@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/magdaahmed (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

HTML5

Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) Wordpress Development

Certifications

data analysis in spread sheets
Build your own chatbot
full stack developement track
Oracle Java Certification: 1. Data
Types

Data Science & Analytics Intro

Magda Ahmed

Front-end Web Developer

Alexandria

Summary

Front-end web developer experienced in building UI with WordPress and creating fully functional WordPress websites, I like both the design aspect because it helps me unleash my creative side while the technical aspect helps me to build logic and solve problems so I find myself enjoying doing both.

Working in IT makes it impossible to get enough or stop learning, so I'll always consider myself a full-time student.

Experience

Voktech Egypt
Web Development Intern
February 2021 - May 2021 (4 months)
remotely

- Worked on WordPress websites (E-commerce, Business Websites, Multilingual websites..etc).
- used page builders(Ex: Elementor, WPbakery..etc) and plugins(translation, seasonal customization..etc).
- used CSS3 for some customization.
- held meetings with clients to understand their needs & their website's functionality.
- handled clients (edits and queries) till their website goes live.

Moneyleek

Frontend Web Developer

October 2020 - November 2020 (2 months)

Alexandria, Egypt

worked on front-end tasks using HTML5, CSS3 & Bootstrap 5

Education

Alexandria University

Bachelor's degree, Management Information Systems · (2016 - 2020)